Guide to the Rice University Office of Admissions records, 1979-2010 UA 142
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series III: Alphabetical Files, 1979-2004, 111342
  - University Organizations: Standing Committees, 1993-1997, 111556 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - University Organizations: Student Database Task Force, 1995, 111557 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - University Organizations: Draft Agreement between UT Houston Health Science Scholarship Foundation, UT-Houston Medical School and Rice University, 2001, 111558 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Visitor Evaluations, 1995-1996, 111559 (Box 30, Folder 15)
- Series IV: Alphabetical files addendum, 1993-2010, 111700
  - Admissions committee: Information and guidelines for application review process, 1994-2003, 111701 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - CIS Central America Tour, 111702 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Denver Counselor Breakfast, Sept. 29, 2005, 111703 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Enrollment statistics and reports, 1993-1997, 111704 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Fayez Sarofim International Scholarships, 2004-2005, 111705 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Important memos, 2001-2005, 111706 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Information on foreign international systems, 1999-early 2000s, 111707 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - International student recruiting, 2006-2007, 111708 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - New York City Counselor Fly-In, Feb. 6-9, 2003, 111709 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - [Rice] Office of International Students and Scholars (OISS), 2005-2009, 111710 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - International students at Rice (students recruiting students), 2004-2005, 111711 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Recruitment Plus, April 2003, 111712 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Rice athletics, miscellaneous material, 2005-2010, 111713 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Report to the Faculty Council Subcommittee on Athletics, 2002, 111714 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - "A Report to the Provost on the Student Database Task Force" by Chandler Davidson, Aug. 16, 1995, 111715 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Report (draft) of the Stategic Planning Committee, 1996, "Rice: The Next Century", 111716 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Research by Chandler Davidson, Chair, Committee on Admissions, pertaining to student athletes at Rice, 1994-2003, 111717 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Society of Families Leadership Committee, 1996, 111718 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Statistics and Retreat notes, 111719 (Box 34, Folder 5-9)
  - Travel: ECIS Conference, 2005, 111720 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Tulane emergency (Hurricane Katrina), 2005, 111721 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Yield models, 2002-2007, 111722 (Box 34, Folder 12-14)